veet a javascript build tool that simplifies the way we build and develop
veet 一个 javascript 构建工具，它简化了我们构建和开发
front-end web applications at its core it does two things one serve your code
前端 Web 应用程序的方式，它的核心是它做两件事，一是在开发期间在本地为您的代码提供服务
locally during development and two bundle your javascript css and other
，二是将您的 javascript css 和其他
assets together for production there are many other tools out there that do the
资产捆绑在一起以进行生产还有许多其他工具 那里
same thing like webpack so what makes vee different well it was created by
和 webpack 做同样的事情，所以vee 的不同之处在于它是由 evan yu 创建的，
evan yu who also created vue.js as a way to both simplify and speed up the build
他还创建了 vue.js 作为一种简化和加速构建
process not long ago web developers had no native way to combine javascript
过程的方式 不久前 web 开发人员没有本地方法来组合 javascript
files together in a modular way this led to tools like webpack and rollup that
文件以模块化的方式组合在一起，这导致了诸如 webpack 和 rollup 之类的工具，
concatenate multiple files together into a single bundle for the browser the
它们将多个文件连接到浏览器的单个包中。
problem is that this process becomes increasingly slow as the app adds more
问题是，随着应用程序
code and dependencies in 2015 ecmascript modules were introduced and by 2020 had
在 2015 年引入更多代码和依赖项，这个过程变得越来越慢 ecmascript模块被引入和 到 2020 年拥有
wide browser support allowing developers to import and export code from different
广泛的浏览器支持，允许开发人员从浏览器中的不同文件导入和导出代码
files in the browser veed leverages native es modules in the browser to load
veed 利用原生 e 浏览器中的 s 模块可立即加载
your code instantly no matter how large the app is it also supports hot module
您的代码，无论应用程序有多大 它还支持热模块
replacement for an extremely fast feedback loop during development when
替换，以便在开发期间实现极快的反馈循环 在
building for production it uses roll up under the hood so you don't have to
构建生产时使用它在引擎盖下滚动，因此您不必
worry about configuring it it's an opinionated tool that provides
担心 关于配置它是一个固执己见的工具，它为大多数开发人员提供开箱即用的
conventions that work out of the box for the majority of developers to get
约定，以便
started run npm netweat from the command line and choose a starter project with
开始从命令行运行 npm netweat并选择一个带有
your favorite front-end framework you'll notice the project comes with a v-config
您最喜欢的前端框架的启动项目，您会注意到该项目来了 使用 v-config
file it has a plug-in ecosystem that can extend it with additional features and
文件，它有一个插件生态系统，可以使用其他功能对其进行扩展，
you can also manually override the roll-up defaults when necessary and
您还可以在必要时手动覆盖汇总默认值，并且
there are some really cool plugins out there like vtssr that can do server-side
有一些非常酷的插件，例如 vtssr 可以做服务器端
rendering like next.js now to serve the application locally run npm run dev even
现在像 next.js 一样渲染以在本地运行 npm run dev
if i install a bunch of big dependencies like low dash and moment the time to run
即使我安装了一堆大的依赖项，比如低破折号和时刻
the dev server does not change now if you open the network tab in the browser
运行开发服务器 doe 如果您在浏览器开发工具中打开网络选项卡，现在不会更改，
dev tools you'll notice that instead of importing a single javascript bundle
您会注意到，它不是导入单个 javascript 捆绑
file it's importing our actual source code like a raw tsx file in this case it
文件，而是导入我们的实际源代码，如原始 tsx 文件，在这种情况下，
also makes typescript about 20 to 30 times faster because it skips type
它还使打字稿大约 20 到 30速度快了很多倍，因为它跳过类型
checking and uses es build to transpile your code now as you're developing your
检查并使用 es build现在在您开发应用程序时转译您的代码，
app you might change the state of it in the ui then realize that some of the
您可能会在 ui 中更改它的状态，然后意识到
code needs to change when you modify the source code the changes will be
当您修改源代码时需要更改一些代码 更改将
reflected instantly without losing the state of the application that's what we
立即反映，而不会丢失应用程序的状态，这就是我们
call hot module replacement now run npm build to build the app for production
所说的热模块替换 现在运行 npmbuild 来构建应用程序以进行生产，
this will generate a javascript bundle with rollup with a bunch of automatic
这将生成一个带有汇总的 javascript 包，其中包含一系列自动
optimizations like automatic code splitting for any dynamic imports and
优化，例如针对任何动态的自动代码拆分 进口和
css this has been beat in 100 seconds if you want to see more short videos like
css这已经在100秒内被击败如果你想看到更多这样的短视频
this hit the like button and subscribe thanks for watching and i will see you
点击喜欢按钮并订阅感谢观看，我会的
in the next one
下次见